Next time, I'll come on a flying car
too.
holiday came again.
Meow.
What is this?
I'm going to show you a video of the
day.
What's your fortune today?
No, no, no.
Ta-da! There's something good!
Yeah!
I'm not excited.
What are you doing?
Are you filming?
We're taking a photo.
Yay!
Butterfly.
Today...
Wait a minute.
Stand in front of the mirror.
Stand in a line.
When you go back, you should do like
this.
Then, go back.
At first, you don't have to move.
Then, you should close your legs.
Everyone, this way.
At the beginning,
At the beginning, at the phrase,
At the phrase, everyone should pass
through here.
Look straight ahead.
Like you're chasing something.
Can I chase you?
Until the day we can't see each other
again.
Can I chase you?
I'm the guitar you play.
I'm your eyes on the stage.
Let's play together.
Thank you for watching.
I'm going to do my best!
Today, we are here at the first part of
the program,
which is called,
Tokimeki-kun from Tokimeki-kun's Lucky
Bag.
Thank you for coming to watch this
program.
Thank you very much.
I'm Angelia, the second member of
Tokimeki Couple.
We are going to start soon.
Please wait for us with excitement and
excitement.
Let's start with Chuu.
Neru and Osho...
Neru and...
Let's hug on New Year's Day and play
with a ball.
Perfect.
Alright!
Thank you for watching!
If you turn off the music, the old lady
will be angry.
Kanamin!
Haruka!
Ria!
Yori!
Go!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for your hard work!
1 minute has ended!
It was a hot live.
We were doing it in the first part, but
we couldn't do it in the second part.
It was the last song of the year.
We couldn't do all the last songs.
That's right.
All the songs are different.
Yes, all the songs in the first part
are different.
I think about it, and I remember each
song.
I did it very carefully.
It was a great live.
I put P.N. on my manager's phone.
I'm going to miss P.N.
Thank you very much.
Let's do our best.
Let's go.
P.N.
Who am I?
Hello, I am Hiori Mikoto, Yoshikawa
Hiori of Tokimeki Green.
I will be performing soon.
This is the last live performance of
2019, so don't leave any regrets!
I think it's a good order.
See you!
OK.
You didn't bite much, did you?
Thank you.
Isn't it amazing?
I think this is the power of magic that
I used to be a toki-kuriru.
I learned the magic of changing clothes
in an instant.
I will continue to use this technique
in 2020.
Yes!
I will do my best in 2020.
Bye bye.
Oh!
They tried not to catch it...
It should have been like this.
Please edit this part.
Let's go!
OK!
What's the order?
It's been a long time since 2019.
It's been a long time since 2010.
Tanami!
Hitoka!
Haruka!
Riria!
Hiyori!
Rock on!
It's been 2019!
Here we go!
The cat's name is Sokoro.
2019 is coming to an end!
Good luck!
Thank you everyone!
Dancer Setsuko Samuera
Most recent dancing anime is...
FIAC
Thank you for watching!
Happy New Year!
Clap clap clap
Let's have fun this year too
Kiss
Oh, you're ready
Do the hand too
Kiss
So cute
How was it? What did you do?
I woke up properly
I slept properly
Oh, you slept?
I saw the light
I slept
I woke up and went to the Joya's house
to make money
Oh, you went to make money every day
Yes
I went shopping and went shopping and
went shopping
How was it? It was cheap
It was cheap
What did you do?
I went to my grandma's house
I ate sushi and climbed a mountain
You climbed a mountain?
Yes
And I started to cut sashimi
Really?
I helped my grandma and cut it
deliciously
Yes
Then, Akiyome
Akiyome
What?
Oh, right
Akiyome
How do you feel?
I ate Ozoni
Ozoni was delicious
The sweet potato was really delicious
The sweet potato, the red sweet potato
was delicious
And
In 2019, the last shopping
I bought a carrot for sweets
At the supermarket
I bought it and haven't eaten it yet
I love that
Isn't it delicious? Carrot
Do you know?
It's not a real carrot, it's a carrot
with rice
It's delicious
Please try it
And
What did I do?
What?
Yes.
I helped my grandmother make osechi.
I want to be able to cook this year.
I'm not good at cooking, so I don't
want to eat it.
I didn't want to cook by myself.
I want to be able to cook when I need
it.
I will do my best to win everyone's
heart with my stomach.
Bye bye.
Please support me this year.
Congratulations!
I'm looking forward to working with you
this year.
Today is...
Today is the 2-shot of Kangol.
It's January 4th.
It's Kibaro.
New Year's.
I made a crab.
It's amazing!
Please line up in the line with your
triangle.
If you don't have a triangle, please
line up in the line.
Yeah! Tokibaro!
Kangaroo!
Yes! Today is January 4th.
It's a two-shot meeting of Kangaroo!
Kanamin is wearing a hat.
Kangaroo!
Oh!
Kanamin!
Kanamin's hat is fresh.
Fresh.
Cute.
The center is off.
Here?
Yeah!
Oh! Cute!
Nail!
Yeah!
Blue color.
Oh!
Yeah! Yeah!
Cute!
I also reproduced the makeup.
Good! Glitter!
Yes!
I'm shining.
The glitter is overflowing.
Overflowing.
I became like Bambi.
Do you have Bambi?
Bambi!
Oh! Ban!
Odango-san!
Yeah! Odango Bambi!
Yeah!
It's a mouse.
Yes! It's a mouse.
So it's easy to pose like a mouse.
Bambi, please pose like a mouse.
Oh! Sorry.
Chu-chu! Chu-chu!
Bambi is like this.
Yeah.
Mustache.
Cat and mouse are like this.
Cat is like this.
Like this?
Yes.
Today is the first day of the special
exhibition.
Yes.
Thank you for your cooperation this
year as well.
I want to see Princess.
Everyone wants to see Princess.
Cinderella?
I've never seen it in real life.
Yellow?
Belle?
I'm so happy.
Pink? What was it?
Not a robot.
What?
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
Bye bye.
Let's go.
This is our third day of skiing.
Is it hot?
It's hot.
I've never done this before, so I don't
know.
It hurts.
Skiing, skiing, skiing...
Please subscribe to my channel.
I like you.
I'm sorry.
I want to play snowball.
I'm scared of snowball.
I can play it.
There is a different person.
Has anyone ever played snowball?
Snowball.
What about skiing?
I think so.
I think skiing is better.
I can't challenge it because I'm
scared.
We're going to sing Happy Birthday to
Ohami Surprise.
It's our first surprise.
Happy Birthday!
I know what it is.
19 years old.
Last teen.
I remember the last teen.
I know it today.
It's the last of the 10 years.
It's the last teen.
This is the last.
I don't know.
It's the last teen.
I don't know when I realize it.
What are you doing?
I feel something.
I understand.
Teenager play.
We are the teen.
So, we take the second generation.
Climb the stairs of adults?
What are you doing?
oooo
Sleeping together?
Yes.
Two of us
I love it!
Wait a minute.
That's not coming.
It's a blink.
Oh, it's a blink.
Bami.
The flowers are in the picture.
I'm setting the flowers.
I can't get out.
Thank you for watching.
Hey, how many times have you recorded
this?
This is the easiest one I've ever done.
You're so good at recording.
Wait, not the song, but the filter.
The one with Saga?
It's more like a prank.
The prank begins!
What?
Spring?
Wow!
It's out!
Eh? The venue?
Wow!
oning
Analyst
Touhou no Yaiba
Celestial
Namsoul
ke
Please subscribe to my channel!